Finding aid for the Henry Clay Frick Papers, Series II: Correspondence, 1882-1929, undated HCFF.1.2
The Frick Collection/Frick Art Reference Library Archives
- Robinson, C.L.F. - Robinson, John (Box 79, Folder 7)
  Robinson, John B., 1889
- Robinson, Margaret - Rock (Box 79, Folder 8)
  Robinson, Margaret Blake, 1905
  Robinson, Thomas, 1904
  Robinson, W.T. (William T.), 1905-1914
  Robison, H.C., 1891
  Rock Island Company (New York, N.Y.), 1903-1906
- Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1899-1922 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Rockefeller, William - Rogers, Henry (Box 79, Folder 10)
  Rockefeller, William, 1909
  Rocky Mountain Club (New York, N.Y.), 1916
  Rodd, Thomas, 1898
  Rodgers, Alice M., 1919
  Rodgers, Samuel, 1909
  Rodgers, W.B., 1897
  Rodgers, William B., 1916-1917
  Roemer, Julius, 1906
  Roessing, Geo. B., 1902
  Rogers, A.J., 1917
  Rogers, Andrew W., 1919
  Rogers, Anne E.S., [1903]
  Rogers, Brown and Company (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1898
  Rogers, Dwight L., 1906
  Rogers, Elias, 1901
  Rogers, George Davidson, 1897-1909
  Rogers, Henry H., 1899-1906
- Rogers, Jacob - Ronnan (Box 79, Folder 11)
  Rogers, Jacob C., 1903-1916
  Rogers, Jesse L., 1893
  Rogers, Oscar, 1914-1921
  Rokely, R.S., 1913
  Rolston and Bass, Bankers and Brokers (New York, N.Y.), 1898
  Rome (Bigot's Plan of Imperial Rome), 1912-1913
  Romeike, Henry, 1889-1901
  Ronnan, Fred P., 1900
- Rood - Rook (Box 79, Folder 12)
  Rood, Albert, 1910
  Rook, C.A., 1902-1919
- Roosevelt, George - Roosevelt Home Club (Box 80, Folder 1)
  Roosevelt, George Eulen, 1919
  Roosevelt Home Club (New York, N.Y.), 1905-1906
- Roosevelt, Theodore, 1902-1919 (Box 80, Folder 2-3)
- Root - Ruhe (Box 80, Folder 4)
  Root, Elihu, Jr., 1911
  Root, Talbot, 1905
  Rosboro, Frank H., 1898
  Rose, H.F., 1902
  Rose, W.M., 1916
  Roseburg, William, 1887, 1898
  Roseburg and Dilworth, Brokers (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1886
  Rosemond, Saml. R., 1903
  Rosenbach Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1917
  Rosensteel, T.W., 1904
  Roseti, F., 1889
  Ross, F.G., 1914
  Ross, James, 1903
  Ross, James F., 1913
  Rossa, J. O'D., 1898
  Roth, [?] (Miss), 1908
  Rothschild and Co., Carrosserie Automobile (New York, N.Y.), 1904, 1909
  Rothweiler, W.J., 1900
  Rott, Louis, 1896, 1898
  Rousseau, Th., 1915, 1917
  Rowe, L.S., 1900-1908
  Rowe, R.E. Thorndike, 1897
  Rowe, Wallace H., 1911
  Rowland, Edward B., 1904
  Royal Ontario Nickel Commission (Toronto, Canada), 1917
  Royal Poinciana Hotel (Palm Beach, Fla.), 1917
  Rubush and Hunter, Architects (Indianapolis, Ind.), 1922
  Rue, L.L., 1903
  Ruhe, F.H., 1901
- Rukett - Rutis (Box 80, Folder 5)
  Rukett, Harold J., 1916
  Rumley, Edward A., 1917
  Rumpelmayer, Augusta, 1899
  Ruoff, Henry Woldmar, 1901
  Rush, Allan C., 1915
  Rush, John, 1900
  Russell, A.G., Jr., 1920-1921
  Russell, Alexander, 1917-1919
  Russell, Andrew, 1916
  Russell, F.C., 1907
  Russell, G.T., 1910
  Russia (re: $50,000,000 Imperial Russian Government External Loan), 1921
  Ruth, L.F., 1897-1909
  Ruther, B., 1912
  Rutherfoord [Rutherford?], Alex H., Jr., 1913
  Rutherford, Le Roy A., 1914
  Rutis, Affonso Arnoldo, 1901
- Rutledge - Saltonstall (Box 80, Folder 6)
  Rutledge, Frank I., 1902
  Rutledge, H.C., 1912
  Ryan, [?], 1918
  Ryan, Thomas F., 1915
  Ryan, William J., 1916
  Ryan, Winifred C., 1910
  Rynearson, Edward, 1903
  S.A. Kean and Co., Bankers (Chicago, Ill.), 1889
  S. Crossland's Sons (New Haven, Pa.), 1893
  S. Shafer and Company (Pineville, Ky.), 1916
  S.P. Griffith and Co., Investment Brokers (Kansas City, Mo.), 1900
  S.S. Pinkerton (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900
  S. Troll (Geneva, Switzerland), 1901
  Sabine, William T., Jr., 1908
  Safe Deposit and Trust Co. of Pittsburgh, Pa. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1908
  Safe Roads Automobile Association [no place], 1912
  Safety-Armorite Conduit Co. (Rankin Station, Pa.), 1901
  Sahlor, C.W., 1902
  Saint Barnabas' Free Home (Gibsonia, Pa.), 1919
  Saint Cloud Country Club (Paris, France), 1915-1916
  Saint Paul's Rectory [no place], 1916
  Sailer and Stevenson, Bankers (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1888-1889
  Salem Water Board (Salem, Mass.), 1911
  Salsbury, F.W., 1906
  Saltonstall, John L., 1909-1915
- Sampson - Sangster (Box 80, Folder 7)
  Sampson, Harriet Gray, 1913
  Sampson, J.G., 1916
  Samson, Adelaide Louise, 1896
  Samson, H., 1919
  Samson, W.L.C., 1896
  Samstag and Hilder Bros. (New York, N.Y.), 1919
  San Francisco Chronicle(San Francisco, Cal.), 1908
  Sanborn, E.C., 1912, 1918
  Sanborn, Guy, 1917
  Sanchez Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  Sander, Charles, 1914
  Sander and Sons (St. Albans, England), 1902-1903
  Sanders, T.J., 1897-1918
  Sanderson, Geo. L., 1904
  Sanderson, Henry, 1916
  Sanger, W.T., 1888
  Sangster, Urania Nott, 1915
- Sans - Sarto (Box 80, Folder 8)
  Sans Bois Coal Co. (Cleveland, Ohio), 1909-1913
  Santa Fe Magazine(Chicago, Ill.), 1914
  Saunders, L. Sharpe, Mrs., 1902
  Sapirstein, N.L., 1903
  Sargent, Allston, 1916
  Sargent, C.S., 1908-1918
  Sargent, John S., undated
  Sargent, Porter E., 1916
  Sartain, William, 1897
  Sarto, Andrea del (re: del Sarto's Madonna and Child), undated
- Satinover - Scarritt (Box 80, Folder 9)
  Satinover, Joseph, 1916
  Satterfield - Hurlbut [illustrators], 1909
  Satterlee, Herbert L., 1915
  Satterlee, Louisa Pierpont (Mrs. Herbert L. Satterlee), 1917
  Saxton, L.D., 1905
  Saward, Frederick E., 1903, 1915
  Saward, Fred. Wm., 1898-1914
  Sawyer, Antonia, 1912
  Sawyer, Mary E., 1901, 1908
  Scandrett, Richard B., 1916
  Scanlon, B.F., 1899
  Scanlon, Jno. F., 1908
  Scarritt, W.R., 1916
- Schaeffer - Schiff (Box 80, Folder 10)
  Schaeffer, Nathan C., 1908
  Schaffmeyer, Ad., 1910
  Schellenberg, F.Z., 1901
  Schenck, S.T., 1906
  Schenley Estate [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1902
  Schiff, Jacob H., 1904-1918
  Schiff, Mortimer L., 1908, 1911
- Schiller - Schoonmaker, Grace (Box 80, Folder 11)
  Schiller, William B., 1904-1915
  Schilling, William, 1897
  Schirmer, R.E., 1907
  Schlatter, Henry, 1897-1898
  Schlesinger, Frank, 1912
  Schley, Grant B., 1904
  Schling, Max, 1918
  Schloesser, A.G., 1916
  Schlosser, Jno. B., 1897
  Schluederberg, Geo. W., 1903
  Schmitt, J.P., 1908
  Schmidt, William, 1916
  Schneeberg, Chas., 1907
  Schnyder, Charles, 1919
  Schoenberger, S., 1919
  School Art League (New York, N.Y.), 1916
  Schooley, M.P., 1897
  Schoonmaker, George B., 1905-1913
  Schoonmaker, Grace, 1911
- Schoonmaker, J.M. - Schoonmaker, Rebekah (Box 81, Folder 1)
  Schoonmaker, J.M., 1887-1916
  Schoonmaker, Nellie T. (Mrs. N.R. Schoonmaker), 1915
  Schoonmaker, Rebekah C., 1901-1905
- Schoonmaker, S.L., 1880s, 1895-1918 (Box 81, Folder 2-6)
- Schoor - Schwab, Charles (Box 81, Folder 7)
  Schoor, H., 1898
  Schottland, Maxime, 1910
  Schubert, Frances, 1906
  Schuchman, Fred., 1898
  Schuette, Robert W., 1919
  Schulte Mining Company (Fredericktown, Mo.), 1916
  Schultz, Geo. W., 1907
  Schurz, Carl L., Mrs., 1916
  Schroeder, Wm. F., 1903
  Schwab, Charles M., 1899-1915
- Schwab, Jonas - Scott, H.M. (Box 81, Folder 8)
  Schwab, Jonas, 1917
  Schwabrow, John, 1903
  Schwan, Albert E., 1902
  Schwartz, F.N., 1906
  Schwartz, J.E., 1886
  Schwartz, John, and F.N. Schwartz, for Estate of James E. Schwartz, 1902
  Schwarzschild, Monroe M., 1915
  Science and Industry(Scranton, Pa.), 1900
  Scientific American(New York, N.Y), 1906-1910
  Scott and Stringfellow (Richmond, Va.), 1905
  Scott, Annie King, no year
  Scott, H.M., 1909
- Scott, Hugh R., 1901-1904 (Box 81, Folder 9-11)
- Scott, Hugh R. (continued), 1904-1919 (Box 82, Folder 1-4)
- Scott, J.M. - Scully (Box 82, Folder 5)
  Scott, J.M., 1899
  Scott, James B., 1891
  Scott, John F., 1898-1907
  Scott, M.V.B., 1891
  Scott, S. Maude, 1913
  Scott, Stevenson, 1919
  Scottdale Church [Scottdale, Pa.], 1910
  Scottdale Observer(Scottdale, Pa.), 1904
  Scottdale Y.M.C.A. [Scottdale, Pa.], 1910-1911
  Scoville, G.S., 1900
  Scranton, J.H., 1911
  Scranton, Walter, 1897-1910
  Scudder, Katharine, no year
  Scull, John I., 1915
  Scully, Arthur M., 1908
  Scully, Painter and Beech (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906, 1909
- Seaboard - Selfridge (Box 82, Folder 6)
  Seaboard Air Line Railway Company (New York, N.Y.), 1921
  Seal, Wm. P., 1905
  Seaman, Jennie L., 1906
  Seamen's Institute/Seamen's Church Institute (New York, N.Y.), 1906-1917
  Sears, Eleonora Randolph, 1912
  Sears, Fred H., 1916
  Sears, Richard, 1916
  Seaver, Frances, 1918
  Seavey, Eugene, 1909
  Seawanhaka Corinthian Yacht Club [New York, N.Y.?], 1906
  Seawood, Louis O., 1915
  Second National Bank (Boston, Mass.), 1912
  Sedelmeyer, Charles, 1898
  Sedgwick, A.K., 1900
  Sedgwick, Robert, 1907, 1910
  Seely Manufacturing Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902
  Seely, Ray, 1912-1913
  Seifert, D.I., 1904, 1906
  Selfridge, Anne F. (Mrs. G.S. Selfridge), 1918
  Selfridge, Susan Kearny, 1911
- Seligman - Semple (Box 82, Folder 7)
  Seligman, A.J., 1906-1907
  Seligman, Edwin R.A., 1907
  Seligman, Isaac N., 1904-1915
  Seligman, M., 1910
  Seligmann, Jacques, 1916-1919
  Sell, John S., 1904
  Sellar, Norrie, 1914, 1918
  Sellman, L.D., 1920
  Selznick, Sol, 1915
  Semple and Thompson (re: South Fork Fishing Club bonds), 1886
  Semple, E.M., 1916
  Semple, William, 1901, 1905
- Sentinel- Shane (Box 82, Folder 8)
  Sentinel(Leisenring, Pa.), 1917
  Serviss, H. Garrett P., Mrs., 1918
  Seventh United Presbyterian Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1918
  Seward, Anne, 1911, 1917
  Seymour, S.L., 1897, 1919
  Seymour, Warren I., 1902
  Shadyside Golf Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1897
  Shade Tree Commission (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1911-1912
  Shady Side Academy (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903
  Shady Side Presbyterian Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1889
  Shaffer, George H., 1918
  Shaffer, Isidor, 1918
  Shallenberger, Frank L., 1905, 1911, undated
  Shallenberger, Lydia ("Nin"), 1903
  Shallenberger, N.S., 1897
  Shane, Sam P., 1886
- Shantz, Vera M., 1920-1922 (Box 82, Folder 9-11)
- Sharp - Shaw, J.F. (Box 83, Folder 1)
  Sharp, John A., 1908
  Sharp, Richard C., 1912
  Sharp, Thomas, 1896
  Sharpsville Furnace Co. (Sharpsville, Pa.), 1888
  Shauk, A.B., 1909
  Shaw, Andrew J., 1901
  Shaw, C.N., 1912
  Shaw Coal Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900-1917
  Shaw, Elisha Douglas, 1914
  Shaw, J.F., 1909
- Shaw, John E., 1899-1905 (Box 83, Folder 2-10)
- Shaw, John E. (continued), 1905-1918 (Box 84, Folder 1-4)
- Shaw, Leslie - Sheldon (Box 84, Folder 5)
  Shaw, Leslie M., 1902-1907
  Shaw, P.A., Mrs., 1915
  Shaw, Quincy A., 1905
  Shaw, R.K., 1900
  Shaw, W.A., 1886
  Shea, Christopher A., 1909
  Shearman and Sterling [no place], 1912
  Shearson, E., 1902
  Sheehan, Joseph C., 1913
  Sheesley, Harry F., 1906
  Sheibley, B.E., 1908
  Sheldon and Sheldon (New York, N.Y.), 1910
  Sheldon, Edward, 1915, 1919
  Sheldon, George R., 1890, 1892
  Sheldon, Mary R. (Mrs. George R. Sheldon), 1908
- Shelton - Shillingford (Box 84, Folder 6)
  Shelton, Arthur B., 1910
  Shepard, James E., 1917
  Shepherd, Francis J., 1915
  Sherbon, B.M., 1897
  Sheridan Electric Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  Sheridan, O.J., 1900
  Sherman, A.F., 1892
  Sherman, Bertha, 1912
  Sherman, Frank Dempster, 1916
  Sherman, Frederic Fairchild, 1915
  Sherman, Herbert A., 1904-1905
  Sherrick, Drusilla E., 1896
  Sherriff, Carrie V., 1901
  Sherry, Louis, 1919
  Sherwood, Kate Brownlee, 1900
  Shields, G.O., 1905, 1908
  Shields, John L., 1897, 1900
  Shillingford, H.T., 1890
- Shimer - Shupe (Box 84, Folder 7)
  Shimer, Herbert M., 1893
  Shinn, Wm. P., 1886
  Shipman, Alice D., 1900
  Shippen, John, 1911-1916
  Shipway, John H., 1915, 1918
  Shiras, Clara (Mrs. W.K. Shiras), 1912
  Shirleys, Ltd. [London, England], 1907
  Shirley, W.R., 1916
  Shockley, D.W., 1911
  Shoemaker, A.T., 1899, 1903
  Shoemaker, J.K.P., 1910
  Shoreham Hotel (Washington, D.C.), 1921
  Short, O.D., 1916
  Shortt, William A., 1911
  Shuldiner, David, 1901
  Shuman, A., 1911
  Shupe, Albert, 1896
  Shupe, B.F., 1896
  Shupe, Sam'l., 1888
- Sickels - Simmons (Box 84, Folder 8)
  Sickels, David Banks, 1914
  Sigler, Schuyler, 1906-1907
  Signard, Berthe, 1906
  Silex Percolator Co. (Boston, Mass.), 1916
  Sill, John T., 1912
  Sill, R.W., 1907-1908
  Silliman, C.H., 1913, 1916
  Simkhovitch, Vladimir Gr., 1910, 1916
  Simmons, J., 1915
  Simmons, J. Edward, 1896-1897
- Simon - Simpson (Box 84, Folder 9)
  Simon, Albert A., Jr., 1906
  Simon Borg and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1897
  Simon, Edmond (Arthur Tooth & Sons), 1898-1901
  Simons, Miriam I., undated
  Simonson, W.A., 1908-1909
  Simonton, Ida Vera, 1913
  Simpkins, M.S., 1912
  Simpkins, Nathaniel S., Jr., 1912-1918
  Simpson, Alfred H., 1917
  Simpson, B.E., 1914
  Simpson, G.L., 1901
  Simpson, R.S., Mrs., 1902
  Simpson, Thacher and Bartlett (New York, N.Y.), 1905-1916
- Sinclair - Slater (Box 84, Folder 10)
  Sinclair and Gage (San Antonio, Tex.), 1916
  Sinclair, William, 1911
  Singer, Arthur J., 1910
  Singer, J.J., 1886
  Singer, John J., 1906, 1912
  Sinnott, John F., 1919
  Sipe, Sam F., 1898
  Sisters of Charity (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1909
  Sisters of the Humility of Mary (Lawrence Co., Pa.), 1892-1909
  Six, Jonkers, 1916
  Sixth Avenue and Grant St. property [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1909
  Skalweit, Richard Arnold, 1903
  Skelly, James, 1897
  Skemp, Robt., 1910
  Slack, John C., 1899, 1901, undated
  Slagle, Oliver, 1904
  Slater, T., 1919
- Sleicher - Sloan, R.H. (Box 84, Folder 11)
  Sleicher, John A., 1909-1915
  Slevin, Chas. H., 1902
  Sloan, John, 1912, 1917
  Sloan, R.H., 1901-1902
- Sloan, R.H. (continued), 1903-1904 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Sloan, Wm. - Smith, Edith (Box 85, Folder 2)
  Sloan, Wm. H., 1904
  Sloane, Wm. D., 1908-1915
  Sloane, William Douglas, Mrs., 1912
  Slosson, Charles Aubrey, 1910
  Small, Maynard and Co., Publishers (Boston, Mass.), 1913
  Small, R.O., 1912
  Smiley, E.R., 1900
  Smith, A.H., 1917
  Smith, Albert Edwin, 1918
  Smith, Alex R., 1896
  Smith and Jaffe, Appraisers and Auctioneers (New York, N.Y.), 1919
  Smith and Mabley (New York, N.Y.), 1902
  Smith, Andrew G., 1914
  Smith, Augustin R., 1902
  Smith, Buchanan, Scott and Gordon (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1929
  Smith, Cecil, Mrs., 1916
  Smith, Charles E.W., 1913
  Smith, Charles Emory, 1908
  Smith, Charles J., 1899
  Smith, Charles K., 1910
  Smith, Charles S., 1903
  Smith, Clara A., 1910
  Smith, E.I., 1907, undated
  Smith, Edith Mills (Mrs. Fred S. Smith), 1913
- Smith, Edmund - Smith, I.H. (Box 85, Folder 3)
  Smith, Edmund D., 1888-1897
  Smith Edward, 1914, 1916
  Smith, Edward D., 1916
  Smith, Frank B., undated
  Smith, Frederick H., Jr., 1899-1915
  Smith, George D., 1915
  Smith, George J., 1908
  Smith, George S., 1912
  Smith Granite Co. (Westerly, R.I.), 1898
  Smith, Henry Oliver, 1916
  Smith, I.H., 1897-1898
- Smith, J.C.B. - Smith, W.H. (Box 85, Folder 4)
  Smith, J.C.B., 1916
  Smith, J.P., Sr., 1919
  Smith, James, Jr., 1912
  Smith, Joseph Linden, 1907
  Smith, M.E.D. (Mrs. Edward I. Smith), 1899
  Smith, Margaret E., 1897
  Smith, Marshall, 1900
  Smith, Robert W., 1902
  Smith, T. Guilford, undated
  Smith, W. Alder, Mrs., 1916
  Smith, W.H., 1894-1912
- Smith, William Watson, 1901-1924 (Box 85, Folder 5-8)
- Smithsonian - Snyder, G.E. (Box 85, Folder 9)
  Smithsonian Institution (Washington, D.C.), 1912, 1915
  Smoot, Reed, 1919
  Smyth, Marriott C., 1898
  Smythe, William H., 1914
  Snaman, E.U., 1910-1918
  Snodgrass, Robert, 1886
  Snow, William F., 1915
  Snow Hill Normal and Industrial Institute (Snow Hill, Ala.), 1922
  Snowden, Stephen L., 1909
  Snyder, Claud, 1916
  Snyder, D.C., 1892
  Snyder, Frank E., 1902
  Snyder, G.E., 1897
- Snyder, H.P. - Société (Box 85, Folder 10)
  Snyder, H.P., 1885-1915
  Snyder, Katharine M., 1919, 1922
  Snyder, U.M., undated
  Snyder, Valentine P., 1903
  Snyder, W.P., 1901
  Social Register Association (New York, N.Y.), 1903, 1912
  Société de la Boulie (Versailles, France), 1920-1921
  Société Française de Bienfaisance, or French Benevolent Society (New York, N.Y.), 1910
- Society - Sohier (Box 85, Folder 11)
  Society and Politics[no place], 1912
  Society of Naval Architects and Marine Engineers [Washington, D.C.], 1907-1914
  Society of Printers (Boston, Mass.), 1915
  Society of the Army of the Potomac (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1899
  Society of the Lying-In Hospital [no place], 1914
  Society Players Film Company (Boston, Mass.), 1916
  Sohier, William D., 1903-1916
- Soho - Southworth (Box 86, Folder 1)
  Soho Baths Settlement House (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1919
  Soldin, S., 1914
  Solomon, Winfield S., 1915
  Solvay Process Co. (Syracuse, N.Y.), 1915
  Somes, Miss [?], 1916
  Sorsby, W.B., 1909
  Soulé, J.E., 1892
  South Fork Fishing and Hunting Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1887
  South Hills Board of Trade (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1909
  South West Connellsville Coke Company (Mt. Pleasant, Pa.), 1899-1900
  South West Natural Gas Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1889-1908
  South West Pennsylvania Railway (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1887-1897
  Southern, B.C., 1899
  Southern Pacific Company (New York, N.Y.), 1907-1910
  Southern Pipe Line Company (Oil City, Pa.), 1913
  Southworth, John R., 1919
- Spalding - Speir (Box 86, Folder 2)
  Spalding-Bidwell Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1898
  Spalding, Walter R., 1911-1912
  Sparks, John, 1915
  Sparta Agricultural and Industrial Institute for Colored Youths (Sparta, Ga.), 1910
  Spear, H.S., 1900
  Spearman, J.J., 1910
  Speer, A.M., 1914
  Speer, Charles E., 1902-1903
  Speer, J.L. Dawson, 1908
  Speer, J. Ramsey, 1911
  Speer, John Z., 1907, 1909
  Speer, Louise D., 1904-1911
  Speir, F.W., 1903
- Spelling - Sperry (Box 86, Folder 3)
  Spelling, Thomas C., 1915
  Spence, Joseph, 1899
  Spencer, C.H., 1886-1892
  Spencer, Robert, 1887-1888
  Spencer Trask and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1917
  Spendley, R.H., 1887
  Spering, Nathan, 1911
  Sperry, T.M., 1898
- Speyer - Squire (Box 86, Folder 4)
  Speyer and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1909-1917
  Speyer, James, 1907-1917
  Spiegel, J.R., 1901
  Spies, Albert, 1901
  Spittall's Detective Agency (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1890
  Spofford, Nathaniel N., 1911
  Sportsmen's Association of Cheat Mountain (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1887-1904
  Sportsmen's Society, Publishers (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1901
  Sprague, Breed and Brown Co. (Beverly, Mass.), 1904, 1912
  Sprague, N.S.S., 1910
  Sprague, Seth, 1902
  Sproul, H.A., 1901
  Sproul, William Cameron, 1919
  Sproull, Theo., 1895
  Spur(New York, N.Y.), 1919
  Squire, Andrew, 1913
- St. Bartholomew's - St. Clair Improvement (Box 86, Folder 5)
  St. Bartholomew's Church (New York, N.Y.), 1910-1922
  St. Clair, George W., 1911
  St. Clair Improvement Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902-1904
- St. Clair Land - St. Xavier's (Box 86, Folder 6)
  St. Clair Land Co. [no place], 1922
  St. Clair Loan and Trust Co. (Kansas City, Mo.), 1889
  St. Cloud Country Club (Paris, France), 1921
  St. David's Society (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1915
  St. Francis Xavier's Church (Moundsville, W.Va.), 1916
  St. John, Charles E., 1897-1902
  St. John, Fordyce Barker, 1915-1918
  St. John's Preparatory College (Danvers, Mass.), 1909
  St. Joseph Academy (Greensburgh, Pa.), 1896
  St. Leo's Rectory (New York, N.Y.), 1908
  St. Luke's Lutheran Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1911
  St. Paul's Orphan Asylum (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1897, 1900
  St. Peter's Evangelical Lutheran Slovak Church (Connellsville, Pa.), 1909
  St. Regis Hotel (New York, N.Y.), 1909, 1911
  St. Vincent de Paul's Day Nursery and School (New York, N.Y.), 1904
  St. Xavier's Academy (Beatty, Pa.), 1912
- Stackelberg - Standard (Box 86, Folder 7)
  Stackelberg, Baron de, 1919
  Stackhouse, Powell, 1892-1909
  Stackpole, Cyrus F., 1903
  Stacy, W.W., 1910
  Stage Society of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  Stallings, Leslie C., 1916
  Stamford National Bank (Stamford, Conn.), 1887-1891
  Standard Accident Insurance Co. (Detroit, Mich.), 1923
  Standard Motor Construction Co. (Jersey City, N.J.), 1911, 1915
  Standard Oil Co. (Bayonne, N.J.), 1907
  Standard Oil Company of New York, Boston and New England Departments (Boston, Mass.), 1908-1912
  Standard Trust Company (New York, N.Y.), 1899
- Stanford - Staub (Box 86, Folder 8)
  Stanford, Edward, 1899
  Stanley, A.O., 1911
  Stansfield, I. Walter, 1909
  Stanton, Julia (Mrs. F. H. Stanton), 1910-1922
  Stanwood, Joseph C., 1912-1915
  Stapel, Chas. C., 1918
  Staples, Arthur, 1898
  Star Encaustic Tile Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1891
  Starbuck, W.H., 1892
  Starek, James F., 1914
  Stark, C.N., 1888
  Starrett, Paul, 1916, 1922
  State Young Men's Christian Association of Pennsylvania (Harrisburg, Pa.), 1907, 1909
  Statler, E.M., 1913
  Statler, Geo. D., 1897
  Staub, W.W., 1903-1914
- Stauffer - Steel (Box 86, Folder 9)
  Stauffer, Jacob S., 1916
  Stauffer, Nellie H., 1910-1911
  Stauffer, W.F., 1915
  Stauft, D.B., 1898
  Stearn Company, Cigar Importers (New York, N.Y.), 1908-1917
  Steel, John B., 1899-1900
- Steele - Sterry (Box 86, Folder 10)
  Steele, Charles, 1901-1918
  Steele, M.J., Mrs., 1901
  Stefanko, Jos., 1886
  Steinberg, Herman, 1913
  Steinmeyer, F., 1914
  Steinway and Sons (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1897
  Stemmler, T.W., Jr., 1911
  Stephens, Charles S., 1900
  Stephens, Gertrude O., 1916
  Stephens, Leroy, 1891-1903
  Stereo-Travel Co. (Corona, N.Y.), 1908
  Sterling Bronze Company (New York, N.Y.), 1901, 1915
  Stern, Carolyn H., 1915
  Stern, Isaac, 1902
  Sterner, Marie, 1918
  Sterrett, Tate, 1908, 1912
  Sterrett Sub-District School (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  Sterrett Sunday School Association (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1920
  Sterry, Fred, 1898-1907
- Stetson - Stevenson (Box 86, Folder 11)
  Stetson, E.J., 1915
  Stetson, Francis Lynde, 1902, 1907
  Stevens and Owens (Tyrone, Pa.), 1891
  Stevens, R.H., 1913
  Stevens Institute of Technology (Hoboken, N.J.), 1915
  Stevenson and Foster Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1913-1918
  Stevenson, C.A., 1900
  Stevenson, H.S., 1890
  Stevenson, Henry W., 1901
  Stevenson, John L., 1891
  Stevenson, Thomas G., 1912-1918
  Stevenson, W.H., 1912
- Stewart - Stimmell[?] (Box 87, Folder 1)
  Stewart, D.G., 1909, 1911
  Stewart, Ed. R., 1916-1917
  Stewart, George R., 1914
  Stewart, H.S.A., 1899
  Stewart, J.B., 1899
  Stewart, James, 1908
  Stewart, Samuel L., 1901
  Stewart, W.C., 1889
  Stewart, William Alvah, 1915
  Stewart, William R., 1913
  Stieren Home and Commercial Phonograph Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900
  Stieren, Rachel Robbins, undated
  Stiles, R.H., 1918
  Stillé, Kate Blackiston (Mrs. Alfred Stillé), 1900
  Stillman, James, 1900-1911
  Stillman, Mary W., 1907
  Stillwell, John E., 1917-1918
  Stillwell, L.B., 1901, 1912
  Stimmell[?], F.H., 1896
- Stires - Stoddard (Box 87, Folder 2)
  Stires, Manning, 1910
  Stirling, Chas. G., Mrs., 1914
  Stirling, J.C., 1889-1891
  Stirling, W.R., 1888-1897
  Stocks/stockholders, undated
  Stockwell, Cassie M., 1900
  Stoddard, Henry R., 1914
  Stoddard, Louis E., 1910
- Stokes - Stone, C.A. (Box 87, Folder 3)
  Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1918
  Stokes, F.W., 1916, 1918
  Stokes, Frederick A., 1916
  Stokes, W.E.D., 1917
  Stolzenbach, A.H., 1897
  Stone and Webster (New York, N.Y.), 1914
  Stone, C.A., 1893-1899
- Stone, George - Stoner (Box 87, Folder 4)
  Stone, George R., 1893
  Stone, J.P., 1901
  Stone, Judson F., 1917
  Stone, Melville E., 1912
  Stone, Minerva C., 1916-1919
  Stone, W.A., 1915-1916
  Stone, William A., 1898-1901
  Stoner, F.S., 1909
  Stoner, Geo., Mrs., 1897
  Stoner, George W., 1897-1914
  Stoner, W.F., 1901
- Stoney, R.J., Jr., 1897-1904 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Storch - Strayer (Box 87, Folder 6)
  Storch, John, 1903, 1912
  Storm, George L., 1915
  Stotesbury, E.T., 1915-1916
  Stothart, Euphie, 1897
  Stott, John E., 1904
  Stott, Katheryn V. (Mrs. Geo. F. Stott), undated
  Stouffer, P.J., 1885
  Stoughton, Bradley, 1917, 1919
  Stovall, Pleasant A., 1918
  Strachan, Maria J., undated
  Strafford, Cora, undated
  Strain, Jno., 1901-1902
  Straithmore, Muriel, 1915
  Strakosch, Carl, 1914
  Strassburger, Ralph B., 1912
  Strasser, L.S., 1901
  Straub and Morris (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1888
  Straub, E.H., Mrs., 1909